Ah yeah yeah
I been ballin
on these niggas
Now watch me
ball on these niggas
Now watch me ball on
these niggas yeah!
I don't really wanna go,
I don't really wanna stay
(don't want to stay)
But I really hope and pray,
Can we get it together,
Get it together
Mustard on that beat ho!
I put the new
forgios on the jeep
I trap until them
Bloody bottoms is underneath
Cause all my niggas
Got it out the streets
I keep 100 racks
Inside my jeans
I remember hitten em all
With the whole team
Now a nigga
can't answer a call
Cause I'm balling
I was waking
up getting racks
In the morning
I was broke now im rich
These niggas salty
All this designer on my body
Got me drip drip
Straight up
out the yachtects
I'm a big crip
If I got a pint of lean
Ima sip sip
I run them racks
up with my queen
Like london and nip
But I got rich
on all these niggas
I didn't forget back
I had to go
through the struggle
I didn't forget that
I hopped
inside of the maybach
And now I sit back
These bitches know me now
Cause I got them big racks
Cause im getting money now
I know you heard that
Young nigga on the corner
Bitch I had to serve crack
Uncle fronted me some p's
Had to get embersed back
We came up on dirty money
I gave it a bird bath
Cut of the brain
And I give my
bitch a new coupe
Either you from
the yacht gang
Or you suwhoop
Got a new
orleans bitch and man
That pussy voodoo
And im that nigga now
Who knew?
I put the new
forgios on the jeep
I trap until them
Bloody bottoms is underneath
Cause all my niggas
Got it out the streets
I keep 100 racks
Inside my jeans
I remember hitten em all
With the whole team
Now a nigga
cant answer a call
Cause im ballin
I was waking
up getting racks
In the morning
I was broke now im rich
These niggas salty
I been waking
To get the money woah woah
Gotta bad bitch
Her ass tatted woah woah
Givenchy to my toes
Two twins im fuckin em both
I put her in new ap
The water like a boat
I was down bad on
Where was you niggas at
I know you
turned your back on me
Just to get some racks
I seen you swerve back
Cause im in black bach
New diamonds on
me fuck a flash
This aint snapchat
Cause I been getting paid
Yellow diamonds on me
Look like lemonade
Got my baby mama
That new bentayga
Trynna get a
dojo like a sensi
Rolls royce umbrellas
when im in the rain
I just mind my business
I got brothers that did the
time I aint kidding
All these rappers just talk
about it I live it
Goin up I ain't got no
sky limit yeah yeah
I put the new
forgios on the jeep
I trap until them
Bloody bottoms is underneath
Cause all my niggas
Got it out the streets
I keep 100 racks
Inside my jeans
I remember hitten em all
With the whole team
Now a nigga
cant answer a call
Cause im ballin
I was waking
up getting racks
In the morning
I was broke now im rich
These niggas salty
Ah yeah yeah
I been ballin
on these niggas
Now watch me ball on these
niggas
Now watch me ball on
these niggas yeah!
Now watch me
ball on these niggas
Now watch me ball on these
niggas yeah yeah!